BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 2180-2249 (Box 47)
  - Lodge 2234, 1930-1973 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 2235, 1929-1979 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 2243, 1928-1974 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 2245, 1948-1974 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 2247, 1933-1970 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- 2250-3005 (Box 48)
  - Lodge 2259, 1949-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2260, 1946-1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2262, 1932-1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2268, 1929-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2269, 1928-1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2270, 1943-1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2273, 1929-1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2276, 1936-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2277, 1941-1972 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 2278, 1945-1972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 2280, 1947-1967 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2281, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Also Lodge 2040. May 19, 1975
  - Lodge 2283, 1945-1972 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2288, 1947-1968 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2290, 1941-1971 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2291, 1943-1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2293, 1946-1971 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2329, 1954-1974 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2345, 1963-1970 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2350, 1966-1974 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 3000 - Discipline: Egbert Hernandez, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 3000 - Discipline: Dinorah Colon, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 3003 - Discipline: Nicholas C. Giraffa, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 3003 - Discipline: Dennis Shanchuck, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 3003 - Discipline: Alexander B. Calder, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 3003 - Discipline: Theodore W. O'Chart, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 3003 - Discipline: W. Bruce Patterson, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 3005 - Discipline: Clifford J. Current, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 3005 - Discipline: Craig Higgins, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 3005 - Discipline: Thelma Reid, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 3005 - Discipline: Robert S. Schickel, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 3005 - Discipline: James H. Wheeler, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- 3006-end (Box 49)
  - Lodge 3008 - Protest by Brother George E. Cook of the nomination and election of Brother William Beatty as Chairman Protective Committee of Lodge 3008, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 3008 - Eligibility: William Beatty to Continue to Serve as Local Chairman, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 3012 - Discipline: Luis Lugo, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 3012 - Discipline: Luis O'Farrill, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 3021, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 3022 - Appeal: R.A. Krause, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Ray Parker, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: C.C. Maule, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Miss Pam S. Christensen, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Miss Geraldine L. Darold, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Edward Fernandez, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Miss Christal Kerrigan, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 3024 - Discipline: Miss Gladys Middleton, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 3026, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 3033 - Discipline: Miss Gloria Dunne, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 3049, 1947-1969 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 3051, 1950-1973 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: H.V. Molle, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: W.P. Conerty, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: F.J. Lawson, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: Norman Marsich, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: Charles Mayer, Junior, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 3055 - Discipline: John Michaud, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- 241-250-146 (Box 50)
  - The Academy of Political Science, 1957-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - The Academy of Political and Social Science, 1956-1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association - Summary of Awards, 1964-1968 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association - Arbitration News, 1959-1969 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Congress of Railway Unions, 1969-1972 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    December 5, 1969-August 29, 1972
  - Congress of Railway Unions - Special C.L. Dennis File, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Seaboard Coast Line/Louisville and Nashville and Southeastern, 1972-1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    January 1, 1972- September 30, 1974
  - Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment - Proceedings of the Twenty-Third Regular Meeting, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    May 30, 1971
  - Protests Louisville and Nashville-Seaboard Coast Line Merger, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    October 1974
  - Board of Adjustment - Baltimore and Ohio, 1966-1970 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Tentative Merger between Missouri Pacific System Board 72 and Frisco System Board 43, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines), 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    July 1972-December 1973
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    January 1974-May 1975
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    January 1972-August 1973
- 250 - 0-13 (Box 51)
  - Board of Adjustment, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Seaboard Coast Line, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Seaboard Air Line, 1963-1970 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Atlantic Coast Line, 1965-1969 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Seaboard Coast Line, 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Tampa Union Station System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1966 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Piedmont and Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1963 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Jacksonville Terminal Company Board of Adjustment, 1923-1967 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Port Utilities Commission Board of Adjustment, 1938-1960 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - Seaboard Coast Line (National Mediation Board NMB Case R-3964: Representation election of mail and train porters Seaboard Coast Line), 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Baltimore and Ohio(Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1972 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Maryland and Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Baltimore and Ohio New York Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1947-1965 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Board of Adjustment - Baltimore and Ohio: Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1947-1965 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Consolidators Freight Handling Corporation - System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Staten Island Rapid Transit Board of Adjustment, 1947-1965 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Belt Railway of Chicago, 1961-1974 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Belt Railway of Chicago - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1973 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Board of Adjustment - Boston and Maine (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1973 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Boston and Maine, 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Boston and Maine, 1963-1966 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Bangor and Aroostook System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1969 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Boston and Maine - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Maine Central, 1922-1960 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Maine Central (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - . (Box 51, Folder 29)
- 14-15 (Box 52)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Lines East, 1970-1972 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Dominion Atlantic Railway (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Toronto Terminals Railway Company System Board of Adjustment, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canada Steamship Lines, Limited, 1961-1965 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Essex Terminal Railway Company System Board of Adjustment, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Quebec Central Railway Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian National Railways, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Lines East, 1967-1969 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway (Eastern and Atlantic Region) - Minutes, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    May 22-23, 1969
  - Canadian Pacific Railway (Eastern and Atlantic Regions) - Minutes, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    June 27-28, 1968
  - Canadian Pacific Eastern and Atlantic Regions Board of Adjustment - Special Meeting, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    January 26, 1968
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Lines East, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific (Eastern Region): Appeal for J. MacPherson; William Irving; F.L. Dossey; and William Hamilton, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Pacific Airlines, Limited, Board of Adjustment, 1958-1965 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Hurst Engineering and Construction Company Limited - System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Maple Leaf Mills Limited, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Northern Alberta Railways System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1965 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Pacific Great Eastern, 1958-1967 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Grain Elevators Canada Board of Adjustment, 1958-1970 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - The Alberta Stock Yards Company Limited System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - The Public Markets, Limited System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1965 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Railway Prairie and Pacific Regions, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Railway, Prairie and Pacific Regions: Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Minutes, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    Bound. October 24-25, 1966.
  - System Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Railway, Prairie and Pacific Regions: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Minutes, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    September 18-19, 1967. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Railway, Prairie and Pacific Regions: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Minutes, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    Bound. September 23-24, 1968
  - System Board of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Railway, Prairie and Pacific Regions: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Minutes, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    Bound. May 4-5, 1970.
- 16-19 (Box 53)
  - Board of Adjustment - Unified System Board of Adjustment 16, 1970-1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Colorado and Southern, Denver and Rio Grande Western (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Colorado and Southern-Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1960-1968 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Colorado and Southern-Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1963-1969 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Colorado and Wyoming, 1949-1967 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Denver and Rio Grande Western Hospital Association, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Denver Union Stock Yards Company, 1947-1967 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Board of Adjustment - Denver Union Terminal, 1922-1967 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Board of Adjustment - Fort Worth and Denver, 1921-1960 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific-Fort Worth and Dallas, 1946-1967 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific-Fort Worth and Dallas (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Ogden Union Stockyards Company, 1949-1968 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Rio Grande Motor Way, Incorporated, 1949-1967 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Board of Adjustment - Salt Lake Union Depot and Railroad Company, 1949-1967 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau, 1949-1967 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - North Salt Lake Live Stock Company (Formerly Salt Lake Livestock Company), 1968 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Pueblo Union Depot and Railroad Company, 1949-1967 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Central Railroad of New Jersey - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Lehigh and New England, 1921-1970 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Chestnut Ridge Railway Board of Adjustment, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - New York and Long Branch, 1964-1966 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Wharton and Northern Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1953-1966 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Board of Adjustment - New York, Susquehanna, and Western - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - New York, Susquehanna, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1966 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Report of Trial Committee Concerning the Evidence Presented at Open Hearing, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    July 24, 1965
  - Board of Adjustment - Central Railroad of New Jersey (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1973 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Board of Adjustment - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1966-1973 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Board of Adjustment - Central Vermont - By-Laws, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Board of Adjustment - Central Vermont, 1956-1974 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- 20-23 (Box 54)
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1964-1968 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Meeting Agenda, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    June 12-13, 1969
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks: "The Modern Union On the Move", 1971 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks: "The Modern Union On the Move", 1971 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Davenport, Rock Island, and North Western (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1971 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks: "The Modern Union On the Move", 1970 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Agreement for Protection of Shopcraft Employees in Event of Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines Merger, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    Received January 2, 1968
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1971 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Keokuk Union Depot Company System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Burlington Refrigerator Express Company Board of Adjustment, 1944-1964 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Davenport, Rock Island, and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1964 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Monon, 1962-1973 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Board of Adjustment - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - The Monon Railroad Company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Ann Arbor Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1969 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Monon Railroad - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Ann Arbor Railroad - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Detroit and Mackinac Railway company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Detroit and Mackinac Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1961 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1961 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Board of Adjustment - Ann Arbor Railroad (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Board of Adjustment - Indianapolis Union Railway Company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Indianapolis Union Railway System Board, 1922-1961 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- 250 - 24-504 (Box 55)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Penn Central Railroad Company, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    February 14, 1975-December 1975
  - Board of Adjustment - Missouri Pacific, 1973-1975 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    June 1973-October 1975
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad, 1972-1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Penn Central Railroad Company, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    January 1, 1974-February 13, 1975
  - System Board of Adjustment - Southern, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - System Boards of Adjustment - Allied Services Division, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    August 1974-December 1975
  - Board of Adjustment - The Reading Company, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Reading By-Laws, 1962-1975 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    July 1962-December 1975
  - System Board of Adjustment - Western Airlines, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    August 1, 1975-December 1975
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Western Lakes District: Report of 20th Regular Meeting, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    July 1970
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Western Lakes District (Express), 1971-1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    January 1, 1971-July 1974
- 24-27 (Box 56)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1973 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Des Moines Union Railway Company (Transportations Communication Union), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Ahnapee and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Des Moines Union Railway, 1921-1965 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Green Bay and Western Board of Adjustment, 1922-1966 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Kewaunee, Green Bay, and Western, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific (East and West), 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific (Lines East and West Consolidated Effective January 1, 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Lines East, 1953-1957 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Lines East, 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Lines East, 1949-1952 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Lines West, 1949-1961 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific, 1945-1948 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific, 1933-1944 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific (East), 1921-1932 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Northwestern, 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and North Western Railway Company (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1971 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Joint Railway Agency - South Saint Paul, Minnesota Board of Adjustment, 1950-1971 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and North Western - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Sioux City Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1950-1958 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago Great Western, 1952-1968 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Fort Dodge, Des Moines, and Southern Board of Adjustment, 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Board of Adjustments - Peoria and Pekin Union (Chicago and Northwestern) - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Board of Adjustment - Toledo, Peoria, and Western (Chicago and Northwestern) - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- 28-43 (Box 57)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Saint Louis San Francisco (Frisco) - By-Laws, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Louis San Francisco (Frisco), 1967-1971 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Louis San Francisco (Frisco), 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Louis San Francisco (Frisco), 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Louis San Francisco (Frisco) (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Sand Springs Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1963 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Alabama, Tennessee, and Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Tulsa Union Depot Board of Adjustment, 1950-1951 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - System Boards of Adjustment - Northeast Oklahoma, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific (Transportation Communications Union), 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Joliet Union Depot, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Rock Island Motor Transit Company, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and Saint Louis, 1963-1966 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    January 1, 1963-June 30, 1966
  - Consolidation System Board of Adjustment Number 42 (Erie-Lackawanna), System Division Number 930 (Erie-Lackawanna) into System Board of Adjustment Number 218 (Norfolk and Western), 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna, 1969-1972 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - By-Laws, 1963-1973 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna (Special Jurisdiction: Lodges 6, 331, 520, 657, 876, 958, 965, 967, and 1230), 1961-1970 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Board of Adjustment - New Jersey and New York, 1963-1968 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Board of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Lackawanna and Wyoming Valley Board of Adjustment, 1940-1963 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Lake Terminal Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1969 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - Appeal of J.J. McBride in the Matter of Chairman Board of Trustees Acting as General Secretary Treasurer, 1965- 1966 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - Appeal of J.J. McBride in the Matter of Filling Vacancy in Office of General Secretary Treasurer, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - Appeal of J.J. McBride in the Matter of General Chairman not Calling a 1965 Meeting of the Board, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Erie Lackawanna - Appeal of J.J. McBride Interpretation of Article 1, Section 15(b) of Protective Laws, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 29)